http://www.nutsonline.com/privacy

ShopOrder online or call800-558-6887SearchYour CartEasy ReorderNeed help?Sign in to your account
* For destinations within the contiguous U.S., orders totaling
$59 or more (before tax) ship free and orders
below $59 ship for $6.99. Multiple shipping
addresses count separately. For other destinations (including international), shipping
cost is calculated at checkout. Delivery date will be estimated at checkout.
See Full DetailsMain ContentNuts & SeedsBest SellersRawOrganicRoastedSalted50% Less SaltUnsaltedIn Shell NutsMixed NutsNutsAlmondsCashewsHazelnuts (Filberts)Macadamia NutsPeanutsPecansPistachiosWalnutsSeedsChia SeedsFlax SeedsHemp SeedsPoppy SeedsPumpkin (Pepitas)Sesame SeedsSquash SeedsSunflower SeedsShop By SpecialtyCacaoCandied & FlavoredChocolate CoveredFlour and MealGrab & Go Snack PacksNut and Seed ButterNut & Plant Based MilksSliced and Chopped NutsShop Organic NutsShop Elmhurst ProductsDried FruitBest SellersChocolate CoveredOrganicNo Sugar AddedNatural Dried FruitMixed FruitFreeze DriedFruit PowdersTropicalDried FruitApricotsCherriesCoconutDatesFigsMangoPineappleRaisinsBerriesBlueberriesCranberriesGoji BerriesMulberriesRaspberriesStrawberriesFruity SnacksFlavored Dried FruitFruit ChipsFruit LeatherFruit SnacksShop by UseDried Fruit for BakingKid-friendly FavoritesShop California Dried FruitShop Sun Dried FruitSuperfood PowdersBest SellersBeet PowderChlorellaMacaSpirulinaNew ProductsActivated CharcoalVitaminsShop by TypeAdaptogenic PowdersBubble Tea PowdersFruit PowdersHerb & Root PowdersMilk & Cheese PowdersNatural SweetenersPlant PowdersProtein PowdersVegetable PowdersOrganic PowdersAdaptogenic PowdersFruit PowdersHerb & Root PowdersPlant PowdersProtein PowdersVegetable PowdersShop by UseBeautyImmunity BoostingMood BoostingPantry EssentialsPerformance BoostingSmoothie SuppliesStress ReducingShop Smoothie SuppliesShop Vitamins & SupplementsChocolates & SweetsBest SellersOrganicSugar FreeVeganCandy by ColorCandy by FlavorWrapped CandyPremium ChocolatesChocolate CoveredDried FruitEspresso BeansMalted Milk BallsNutsPretzelsSeedsClassic CandiesFruit SlicesGummiesHard CandyJelly BeansJordan AlmondsLicoriceM&MsNonpareilsShop by SpecialtyCandy SticksChocolate BarkChocolate RocksFudgeIce Cream ToppingsNovelty CandyOld Time CandyRock CandySalt Water TaffyShop Chocolate-CoveredShop Sugar-FreeSnacksSnacks by ValueOrganicGluten-FreeVeganSproutedRawSnacks by RegionAsian SnacksIndian SnacksFeel Good SnacksCustom Trail MixTrail MixDried FruitEnergy SquaresFruit & Veggie ChipsGranola & MuesliNut BarsNuts & SeedsWhole Wheat BarsSalty SnacksCorn NutsCrackersHalf Popped PopcornOlives & Cured MeatPopcornPretzelsSesame SticksSoy Beans & EdamameSavory SnacksCheesy SnacksJerkySpicy SnacksSnacks by ActivityLunchboxShop Grab & GoMake Your Own Mix!Coffee & TeaCoffee by RoastLight RoastMedium RoastDark RoastShop by TypeDecafFlavored CoffeeHouse BlendTurkish CoffeeCoffeesBrazilColombiaCosta RicaEthiopiaGuatemalaKenyaPanamaSumatraTeaBlack & ChaiBubble TeaDecafGreen & MatchaHerbal & FlavoredIced TeaOolongRooibosShop by SpecialtyChicoryCoffee PodsHot ChocolateNut & Plant Based MilksSweetenersShop Coffee Sample PackShop Herbal TeasCookingShop by ValueOrganicGluten-FreeSproutedCooking StaplesHerbs, Spices & SaltsLeaveners & ThickenersOils & VinegarsPantry EssentialsBeans, Peas & LentilsFreeze Dried VegetablesMushroomsFloursGrainsFarroQuinoaRicePantry EssentialsArtisanal PastasBread Crumbs & StuffingCondimentsJams & JelliesNoodlesNut & Seed ButtersNut & Plant Based MilksSaucesSoup BasesShop by LifestyleKetoKid-friendlyPaleoVeganWhole 30Herbs & SpicesShop Whole 30BakingShop by ValueOrganicGluten-FreeVeganFloursGluten-Free FloursGrain FloursNut FloursNuts & Dried FruitsCoconutDried Fruit for BakingGlazed FruitNuts for BakingBaking ChocolateChips & WafersToppingsCandy by ColorNonpareilsPearlsSanding SugarSprinklesCacaoBaking EssentialsBaking MixesBaking SpicesCocoa PowderExtracts & FlavoringsFillings & PastesLeaveners & ThickenersNut ButtersNut & Plant Based MilksSweetenersShop Gluten-FreeShop Vegan BakingGiftsGiftsHoliday Gift GuideAnniversariesBirthdaysCongratsCorporate GiftingGet WellSympathyThank YouMore Ways to ShopGifts under $30Gifts under $70Premium GiftsGifts that Give BackGifts by TypeBest SellersBasketsCustom MixesCustom TraysTinsTraysGifts by FlavorChocolateFruitySavorySaltyShop Valentine's Day GiftsStart Building Your TraySpecialtiesEasy ReorderSign InNewGiftsShop By DietNuts & SeedsDried FruitSuperfood PowdersChocolates & SweetsSnacksCoffee & TeaCookingBakingVitaminsVariety PacksMy AccountEasy ReorderMy FavoritesMy OrderGift CardsHelpGiftsBest SellersCustom GiftsCustom MixesCustom TraysBy TypeBasketsTinsTraysBy PriceGifts under $30Gifts under $70Premium GiftsGifts that Give BackBy OccasionHoliday Gift GuideAnniversariesBirthdaysCongratsCorporate GiftingGet WellSympathyThank YouShop All GiftsBy FlavorChocolateFruitySavorySaltyGifts that Give BackShop By DietOrganicGluten FreeSugar FreeVeganSproutedKosherPaleoKetoNuts & SeedsBest SellersRawOrganicRoastedSalted50% Less SaltUnsaltedAll NutsAlmondsBrazil NutsBaru NutsCacaoCashewsChestnutsCoconutHazelnuts (Filberts)In Shell NutsMacadamia NutsMixed NutsPeanutsPecansPili NutsPine NutsPistachiosSliced & Chopped NutsTiger NutsWalnutsShop All NutsAll SeedsChia SeedsFlax SeedsHemp SeedsPoppy SeedsPumpkin (Pepitas)Sesame SeedsSquash SeedsSunflower SeedsWatermelon SeedsShop All SeedsCandied & FlavoredChocolate CoveredFlour & MealNut & Seed ButterNut MilkDried FruitBest SellersOrganicNo Sugar AddedDried FruitApricotsCherriesCoconutDatesFigsMangoPineappleRaisinsShop All Dried FruitBerriesBlueberriesCranberriesGoji BerriesMulberriesRaspberriesStrawberriesShop All BerriesFruity SnacksFlavored Dried FruitFruit ChipsFruit LeatherFruit SnacksMixed FruitNatural Dried FruitFreeze DriedChocolate CoveredSuperfood PowdersBest SellersPowdersAdaptogenic PowdersFruit PowdersHerb & Root PowdersMilk & Cheese PowdersPlant PowdersProtein PowdersVegetable PowdersShop All PowdersOrganic PowdersAdaptogenic PowdersFruit PowdersHerb & Root PowdersPlant PowdersProtein PowdersVegetable PowdersShop All Organic PowdersShop By UseBeautyImmunity BoostingMood BoostingPantry EssentialsPerformance BoostingSmoothie SuppliesStress ReducingChocolates & SweetsBest SellersOrganicSugar FreeChocolate CoveredDried FruitEspresso BeansMalted Milk BallsNutsPretzelsSeedsShop AllClassic CandyFruit SlicesGummiesHard CandyJelly BeansJordan AlmondsLicoriceM&MsNonpareilsShop AllSpecialty CandyCandy SticksChocolate BarkChocolate RocksFudgeIce Cream ToppingsNovelty CandyOld Time CandyRock CandySalt Water TaffyVeganCandy by ColorCandy by FlavorWrapped CandyPremium ChocolatesSnacksTrail MixOrganicGluten-FreeFeel Good SnacksCustom Trail MixDried FruitEnergy SquaresFruit & Veggie ChipsGranola & MuesliNut BarsNuts & SeedsWhole Wheat BarsSalty SnacksCorn NutsCrackersHalf Popped PopcornOlives & Cured MeatPopcornPretzelsSesame SticksSoy Beans & EdamameShop All Salty SnacksSavory SnacksCheesy SnacksJerkySpicy SnacksEthnic SnacksAsian SnacksIndian SnacksVeganSproutedRawCoffee & TeaCoffeeLight RoastMedium RoastDark RoastDecafFlavored CoffeeHouse BlendTurkish CoffeeShop All CoffeeTeaBlack & Chai TeaBubble TeaDecaf TeaGreen & MatchaHerbal & FlavoredIced TeaOolongRooibosSpecialtyChicoryCoffee PodsHot ChocolateNut MilksSweetenersCookingOrganicGluten-FreeSproutedPantry EssentialsArtisanal PastasBeans, Peas & LentilsBread Crumbs & StuffingCondimentsFloursMushroomsFreeze Dried VegetablesGrainsHerbs, Spices & SaltsJams & JelliesLeaveners & ThickenersNoodlesNut ButtersNut MilksOils & VinegarsSaucesSoup BasesShop By LifestyleKetoKid-friendlyPaleoVeganWhole 30BakingBest SellersRawOrganicRoastedSalted50% Less SaltUnsaltedAll NutsAlmondsBrazil NutsBaru NutsCacaoCashewsChestnutsCoconutHazelnuts (Filberts)In Shell NutsMacadamia NutsMixed NutsPeanutsPecansPili NutsPine NutsPistachiosSliced & Chopped NutsTiger NutsWalnutsShop All NutsAll SeedsChia SeedsFlax SeedsHemp SeedsPoppy SeedsPumpkin (Pepitas)Sesame SeedsSquash SeedsSunflower SeedsWatermelon SeedsShop All SeedsCandied & FlavoredChocolate CoveredFlour & MealNut & Seed ButterNut MilkOrganicRawGluten-freeDark ChocolatePantrySuperfoodsSingle ServesWholesaleOffice SnacksNew ProductsTop Sellers
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: September 9, 2020
Thank you for visiting the Nuts.com website located at www.nuts.com (the “Site”).
The Site is an Internet property of Nuts.com, Inc. (“Nuts.com,” “we” or “our”). This Nuts.com
Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers our treatment of
personal information and other information that we collect when end-users (“User”,
“you” or “your”): (a) access or use
the Site; (b) access and/or download any of the: (i) text, audio, video, photographs, graphics, artwork,
testimonials
and/or other content featured on the Site (collectively, “Informational Content”); and/or (ii) links
to third
party
websites, products and/or services (“Third-Party Links”, and together with the
Informational
Content, the
“Content”);
(c) access links to Nuts.com's social media pages/accounts (collectively, “Social Media
Pages”)
on
third-party social
media websites, such as Facebook®, Instagram®, LinkedIn®, Pinterest®, Twitter® and
YouTube® (“Social Media Websites”);
(d) purchase Nuts.com products featured on the Site (collectively, “Nuts.com
Products”); (e)
register to
receive the
Nuts.com e-mail newsletter (“Newsletter”); and/or (f) utilize the various contact
forms and/or
contact
information made
available on the Site as a means to contact directly, or request to be contacted by, Nuts.com (collectively, the
“Contact Services,” and together with the Site, Content, Social Media Pages,
Nuts.com Products
and
Newsletter, the “Site
Offerings”). Please note, if you are a resident of a European Union Member State, you are not
permitted to use the Site
and/or Site Offerings.
Users with disabilities who wish to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format can contact us by
e-mailing us at: care@nuts.com; by calling us at: 1-800-558-6887 or by
sending us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125
Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings set forth in the Nuts.com Website Terms and
Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF
THIS PRIVACY
POLICY IN
THEIR ENTIRETY,
YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE OFFERINGS.
Instagram® and Facebook® are registered trademarks of Facebook, Inc.
LinkedIn® is a
registered trademark of
LinkedIn Corporation. Pinterest® is a registered trademark of Pinterest, Inc. Twitter® is a
registered trademark
of Twitter, Inc. YouTube® is a registered trademark of Google, Inc. Please be advised that Nuts.com is
not in
any way affiliated with Facebook, nor are the Site Offerings endorsed, administered or sponsored by any of
the
aforementioned entities.
Your California Privacy Rights
Shine the Light. If you are a resident of the State of California and
would like to learn how
your
“personal information” (as defined in the Shine the Light Law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83) is shared
with third
parties, what categories of personal information we have shared with third parties in the preceding year, as
well as the names and addresses of those third parties, please e-mail us at: care@nuts.com; call us at: (800)
558-6887; or send us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
Further, if you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your
personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: care@nuts.com; call us at:
(800) 558-6887; or send us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016. Please be advised that
where California State residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such
individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law.
Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). In addition to the foregoing, if
you are a
resident of
the State
of California certain other privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the CCPA, including the
right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal
information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the
preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of
third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for California
Residents”;
below for a more complete description of your rights
under
the CCPA as a California State resident.
Privacy Policy Quick Links
Below are links to key sections of our Privacy Policy:
Your Nevada Privacy Rights
Personal Information Collected
Use and Sharing of Personal Information
Non-Personal Information Collection and Use
Credit and/or Debit Card Transactions
Security of Your Personal Information
Children's Privacy
Opt-Out/Unsubscribe
Deleting, Modifying and Updating Your
Information
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Your Nevada Privacy Rights
If you are a resident of the State of Nevada and would like to opt-out from the sale of your personal
information to any third party data broker, please e-mail us at: care@nuts.com;
call us at: (800) 558-6887; or
send us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
Personal Information Collected
Please see our Privacy Provisions for California Residents below for
additional details regarding the categories of personal information collected.
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” shall mean
individually
identifiable
information
from or about an individual. We collect personal information when you access certain of the Site Offerings and
complete the required information request form(s) and/or otherwise provide such information to us. The
information that you must supply on the form(s) may include, without limitation: (a) your name; (b) your
mailing/billing address (where purchasing Nuts.com Products); (c) your e-mail address; (d) your telephone
number; (e) your credit card information (where purchasing Nuts.com Products); and/or (f) any other information
requested by us on the Form.
For purposes of this Privacy Policy, item (e) in the preceding paragraph will be considered “Sensitive
Information.”
Use and Sharing of Personal Information
Please see our Privacy Provisions for California Residents below for
details regarding our use and sharing of personal information.
Nuts.com will never share, sell, rent, exchange or barter your personal information to or with any third-party
for financial gain or marketing purposes. By making your personal information available to Nuts.com, you grant
Nuts.com the right, subject to applicable law, to use that personal information (other than Sensitive
Information) to contact you by telephone and email regarding your use of the Site Offerings (including in
connection with any purchase of Nuts.com Products). If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us,
please follow the instructions at the end of each such marketing message or see the
"Opt-Out/Unsubscribe"
section below. We may also use your personal information to send you promotional messages regarding various
Nuts.com products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services that we think may be of
interest to you. If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us, please follow the instructions at
the end of each such marketing message or use any of the other options available in the
“Opt-Out/Unsubscribe”
section below.
Where you submit personal information, we use the personal information that you make available to facilitate
the delivery of the applicable Site Offerings to you, including to respond to any inquiries made by you. You
also agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem
appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Site Offerings, and to keep you
informed of our other products and services.
We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include
processing credit card and other payment transactions, sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate
information from User lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these
limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our Users' personal information (including Sensitive
Information, where applicable) as needed to perform these functions for us, but we do not permit them to use
User personal information for other purposes.
We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may
request, to customize your experience with the Site Offerings and/or to contact you for market research
purposes. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and
managing our service offerings including, without limitation, the Site Offerings. We may also combine the
information we have gathered about you with information from other sources.
By submitting your personal information by and through the Site Offerings, you agree that such act constitutes
an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as
amended from time to time (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call
regulations. As such,
notwithstanding
that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, and/or on
applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the
Rule and applicable state do-not-call regulations.
Where you provide “prior express consent” within the meaning of the Telephone
Consumer
Protection Act (47 USC §
227), and its implementing regulations adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (47 CFR § 64.1200), as
amended from time-to-time (“TCPA”), you consent to receive, from Nuts.com,
telephone calls,
including artificial
voice calls, pre-recorded messages and/or calls (including text alerts via SMS text messages delivered via
automated technology, to the telephone number(s) that you provided. Please note that you are not required to
provide this consent in order to obtain access to the Site Offerings, and your consent simply allows Nuts.com to
contact you via these means. Please be advised that by agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are
obligated to
immediately inform us if and when the telephone number that you have previously provided to us changes.
Without
limiting the foregoing, if you: (a) have your telephone number reassigned to another person or entity; (b)
give
up your telephone number so that it is no longer used by you; (c) port your telephone number to a landline or
vice versa; or (d) otherwise stop using that telephone number for any reason (collectively “Phone
Number
Change”), you agree that you shall promptly notify Nuts.com of the Phone Number Change via e-mail
at:
care@nuts.com, or by using one of the methods set forth in the
“Contact Us” section
below.
We reserve the right to release current or past personal information (including Sensitive Information): (i) in
the event that we believe that the Site Offerings are being or have been used in violation of the Terms and
Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; (ii) if the information is subpoenaed; provided, however, that, where
permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena,
prior to disclosure of any personal information pursuant to a subpoena; or (iii) if we are sold, merge with a
third-party, are acquired or are the subject of bankruptcy proceedings; provided, however, that if Nuts.com is
involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be
notified via e-mail and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal
information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your personal information.
You hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole
discretion, determine the disclosure to be required by applicable law, including sharing your e-mail address
with third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to
time, and other e-mail marketing laws. Users should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy
Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or
transferred to third-parties without permission.
Credit and/or Debit Card Transactions
Nuts.com utilizes third-party service providers to provide credit and debit card payment processing services.
If you choose to purchase Nuts.com Products, the credit or debit card information provided will be shared with
our contracted third-party payment processing service provider(s). Nuts.com requires that its third-party
payment processing service provider(s) has/have in place privacy policies and practices consistent with this
Privacy Policy; provided, however, that we cannot guarantee the privacy practices of our third-party payment
processing service provider(s).
Non-Personal Information Collection and Use
Please see our Privacy Provisions for California Residents below for
more details regarding the categories and types of non-personal information collected.
Computer IP Addresses/Browser Type
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you and your desktop computer when you
visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation,
the type of browser that you use (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of
operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider
(e.g., Verizon, AT&T). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design
and content of the Site Offerings and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this
information in the aggregate to analyze usage of the Site Offerings.
Cookies
When a User visits the Site, we send one (1) or more cookies and/or gif files (collectively,
"Cookies") to
assign
an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable User's computer and/or mobile device, as applicable. A Cookie
is
a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies
have many benefits to enhance your experience on the Site, as applicable. To find out more about Cookies, please
visit www.cookiecentral.com. We use Cookies to improve the quality of the Site Offerings, including for storing
User preferences and tracking Site usage (such as pages opened and length of stay at the Site, as applicable).
Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all
Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the
instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a User rejects a Cookie, he or she
may still use the Site Offerings; provided, however, that certain functions of the Site Offerings may be
impaired or rendered inoperable if the use of Cookies is disabled. We reserve the right to retain Cookie data
indefinitely.
Behavioral Tracking
Nuts.com and its third-party partners use Cookies, pixels and other tracking technology (collectively,
"Tracking
Technology") to analyze trends, administer the Site, track Users' movements around the Site and to gather
demographic information about our User base as a whole. In addition, we partner with third-parties such as
Facebook to use Tracking Technology in connection with the serving of our advertising to you on other websites
when you exit the Site. Our third-party partners may use Tracking Technology to gather information about your
activities on the Site and other websites in order to provide you with certain Nuts.com advertising based upon
your browsing activities and interests.
Users may be able to disable some, but not all, of this tracking activity by utilizing the "Do Not
Track"
setting or similar options within most major Internet browsers. Further, Users may be able to opt-out of this
form of tracking utilizing the options made available by the Network Advertising Initiative,
Facebook or Digital
Advertising Alliance. Please note that opting out of
this
tracking activity does not opt you out of being served advertising. Even where you opt out of this tracking
activity, you will continue to receive generic ads.
Cross Device Tracking
Nuts.com tracks Users' use of the Site Offerings across various devices, including your personal computer and
mobile device, in order to optimize and personalize your Site Offerings experience. Nuts.com may collect certain
of your personal information across various devices. Please be advised that where you opt-out of having your use
of the Site Offerings tracked across devices, you may need to upload certain information multiple times and/or
input your log-in information multiple times.
Aggregate Data
Nuts.com reserves the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about Users of the Site Offerings
for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and other
characteristics of Users as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information.
Social Media Websites
If you engage in any interaction with Nuts.com, other Users or any third-party on any Social Media Pages, you
should be aware that: (a) the personal information that you submit by and through such Social Media Pages can be
read, collected and/or used by other Users of these websites/services (depending on your privacy settings
associated with your accounts with the applicable Social Media Websites), and could be used to send you
unsolicited messages or otherwise to contact you without your consent or desire; and (b) where Nuts.com responds
to any interaction on such Social Media Pages, your account name/handle may be viewable by any and all
members/Users of Nuts.com's social media accounts. We are not responsible for the personal information that you
choose to submit on any Social Media Websites.
Your interactions with the Social Media Pages are governed by the privacy policies of the applicable Social
Media Websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings of the Social Media Pages with
which you interact to help you understand those Social Media Websites' respective privacy practices. If you have
questions about the security and privacy settings of any Social Media Pages that you use, please refer to the
applicable Social Media Website's privacy notices or policies.
Third-Party Websites
This Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites including, without limitation, Social
Media Websites, as well as the websites of other third parties. Nuts.com is not responsible for the privacy
practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of
these third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a
credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have
separate privacy and data collection practices and Nuts.com has no responsibility or liability relating to them.
Security of Your Personal Information
We endeavor to safeguard and protect our Users' personal information. When Users make personal information
available to us, their personal information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain
any personal information offline). Where our registration/application process prompts Users to enter Sensitive
Information (such as medical information, driver's license/ID card number, health insurance information, data
collected from an automated license plate recognition system, Social Security Number and credit card
information), and when we store and transmit such Sensitive Information, that information is encrypted with
advanced TLS (Transport Layer Security).
Access to your personal information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable security measures to ensure that
your personal information is not accessible to the public. All of our Users' personal information is restricted
in our offices, as well as the offices of our third-party service providers. Only employees or third-party
agents who need User personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to User personal
information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all User personal information.
Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. The servers that we store User
personal information on are kept in a secure physical environment. We also have security measures in place to
protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control.
Please be advised, however, that while we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no
storage facility, technology, software, security protocols or data transmission over the Internet or via
wireless networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Computer hackers that circumvent our security measures
may gain access to certain portions of your personal information, and technological bugs, errors and glitches
may cause inadvertent disclosures of your personal information; provided, however, that any attempt to breach
the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software may constitute a crime
punishable by law. For the reasons mentioned above, we cannot warrant that your personal information will be
absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through the Site, other Site Offerings or otherwise via the
Internet or wireless networks, is done at your own risk.
In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory
agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information.
You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in
order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial
measures.
Children's Privacy
Please see our Privacy Provisions for California Residents below for
more details regarding the personal information of minors.
Visitors under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at
the Site. Nuts.com does not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under eighteen (18) years of
age.
Opt-Out/Unsubscribe
Please see our Privacy Provisions for California Residents below for
instructions on how California Residents can opt-out of the sale of their personal information to third parties.
To opt-out of receiving e-mail and other forms of communication from us, you can: (a) follow the instructions
included in the applicable e-mail message or other communication; (b) update your e-mail communication
preferences in your Account Settings here; or (c) e-mail us at: care@nuts.com.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information
relating to your request for Site Offerings, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. To
opt-out of receiving Site Offerings-related and/or inquiry response-related messages from Nuts.com, you must
cease requesting and/or utilizing the Site Offerings and/or cease submitting inquiries to Nuts.com, as
applicable.
Deleting, Modifying and Updating Your Information
Please see our Privacy Provisions for California Residents below for
instructions on how California Residents can access and/or delete personal information that we have collected.
At your request, we will: (a) inform you of what personal information we have on file for you; (b) amend the
personal information that we have on file for you; and/or (c) remove personal information that you have provided
to us, or that we have otherwise collected. You may do so by e-mailing us at: care@nuts.com. We ask individual
Users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before
processing such requests, and, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we may decline to process requests
that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the
privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on
backup tapes).
Please be advised that deleting your personal information may terminate your access to certain of the Site
Offerings. If you wish to continue using the full complement of Site Offerings, you may not be able to delete
all of the personal information that we have on file for you.
Please be further advised that, after you delete your personal information, residual copies may take a period of
time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.
Transfer of Personal Information Internationally
If you are visiting the Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your
communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting
the Site and/or otherwise communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers. Even if your
jurisdiction does not have the same privacy laws as the jurisdiction where our servers are located, we will
treat your information as subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Nuts.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Site
that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personal information changes, Nuts.com
will notify Users by: (a) sending the modified policy to our Users via e-mail; and/or (b) by any other
reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not
we use your information in this different manner and we will only use your information in this different manner
where you opt-in to such use.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices in general, you may e-mail us as
at: care@nuts.com; call us at: (800) 558-6887; or send us U.S. mail to:
Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ
07016.
Privacy Provisions for California Residents
These Privacy Provisions for California Residents (“Privacy Provisions”)
supplement, and do not
limit in any
way, the Privacy Policy set forth above. These Privacy Provisions apply solely to residents of the State of
California (“CA Users”). We adopt these Privacy Provisions in compliance with the
California
Consumer Privacy
Act of 2018 (“CCPA”).  Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when
used in these
Privacy
Provisions. CA Users with disabilities who wish to access these Privacy Provisions in an alternative format can
contact us by emailing us at: care@nuts.com; calling us at: (800) 558-6887;
or sending us U.S. mail to:
Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
Categories of Information We Collect
We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with,
or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular CA User or device (“personal
information”). In particular, we have collected the following categories of personal information from CA
Users
within the last twelve (12) months:
Category
Examples
Collected
A. Identifiers.
A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol
address, email address, account name, telephone number, or other similar identifiers.
YES
B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code §
1798.80(e)).
A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, postal address,
telephone number, passport number, driver's license or State identification card number, insurance policy
number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card
number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some
personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories.
YES
C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.
Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital
status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender
expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or
military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information).
NO
D. Commercial information.
Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other
purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
YES
E. Biometric information.
Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract
a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and
voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or
exercise data.
NO
F. Internet or other similar network activity.
Browsing history, search history, information on a CA User's interaction with a website, application or
advertisement.
YES
G. Geolocation data.
Physical location or movements.
NO
H. Sensory data.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
NO
I. Professional or employment-related information.
Current or past job history or performance evaluations.
NO
J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C.
Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)).
Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting
on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes,
student financial information, or student disciplinary records.
NO
K. Inferences drawn from other personal information.
Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions,
behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
NO
Personal information does not include:
Publicly available information from government records.
De-identified or aggregated CA User information.
Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, such as:
health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996
(HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data; and
personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit
Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act
(FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.
We obtain the categories of personal information listed above (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address;
(c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) from the following categories of
sources:
Directly from our CA Users. For example, from online registration forms that our CA Users submit to us in
connection with the products and/or services that we offer by and through the Site. (Categories A, B and D)
Indirectly from our CA Users. For example, through information we collect from our CA Users in the course of
providing our products and/or services to them. (Categories A, B, D and F)
Directly and indirectly from activity on the Site. This includes the type of browser that the CA User uses
(e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), CA User IP address, the type of operating system used by the CA
User (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of the CA User's Internet Service Provider. In addition, we
obtain certain Site usage details and analytics as same are collected automatically by us and our third party
partners. (Category F)
When our CA Users interact with us on our social media accounts, including commenting on and/or liking our
posts. (Categories A, B, D and F)
From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the products and/or services that we offer to
our CA Users. For example, third party entities that assist us in sending direct and electronic mail,
targeting advertisements, removing duplicate information from CA User lists, analyzing data and providing
marketing analysis. (Categories A, B, D and F)
Use of Personal Information
We may use or disclose the personal information that we collect (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing
address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) for one or more of the
following business purposes:
To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you provide us with
personal information in connection with your request for products and/or services, we will use that
information to process your request. (Categories A, B, D and F)
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. (Categories A, B, D and F)
To create, maintain, customize and secure your account with us. (Categories A, B, D and F)
To provide you with e-mail, direct mail and telemarketing messages concerning certain Nuts.com products and/or
services, as well as third-party products and/or services, that we believe may be of interest to you.
(Categories A, B, D and F)
To deliver relevant Site content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the
advertising we serve to you. (Categories A, B, D and F)
To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and
us, including the Site's Terms and Conditions. (Categories A, B, D and F)
To improve the Site and better present its contents to you. (Categories A, B, D and F)
For customer service purposes and to respond to inquiries from you. (Categories A, B, D and F)
For testing, research, analysis and product development. (Categories A, B, D and F)
As necessary or appropriate to protect our rights, property or safety, and that of our customers or others.
(Categories A, B, D and F)
To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental
regulations. (Categories A, B, D and F)
As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
(Categories A, B, D and F)
To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or
transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or
similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred. (Categories A,
B, D and F)
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected
for materially different, unrelated or incompatible purposes without providing you with notice.
Sharing Personal Information
Subject to your right to opt-out of such sharing/sale, we may share your personal information (including (a)
name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information)
for the other business purposes set forth above.
When we disclose personal information to a third party service provider or other entity, we enter into a
contractual relationship that describes the purpose for which such third party may use the personal information
and requires that third party to both keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose
other than the performance of its services under the applicable contract. Please note, we do not collect
information from CA Users that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age and we do not share or
sell the personal information of CA Users that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age.
Without limiting the foregoing, we have not shared or sold the personal information of CA Users that we actually
know are less than sixteen (16) years of age in the preceding twelve (12) months.
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information
(including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card
information) for a business purpose:
Category A Identifiers.
Category B California Customer Records personal information categories.
Category D Commercial information.
Category F Internet or other similar network activity.
We disclose your personal information (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d)
telephone number; and (e) credit card information) for a business purpose to the following categories of third
parties:
Our affiliates. (Categories A, B, D and F)
Service providers. (Categories A, B, D and F)
Third parties who provide the products and/or services featured on the Site. (Categories A, B, D and F)
Third parties to whom you authorize us to disclose your personal information in connection with the products
and/or services that we provide to you. (Categories A, B, D and F)
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have not sold any personal information to third parties, or shared your
personal information with third parties for marketing purposes.
Your Rights and Choices
The CCPA provides CA Users (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information.
This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.
Opt-Out from the Sale of Your Personal Information
You have the right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information to third parties. To exercise your right
to opt-out of our sale of your personal information to third parties, please submit a verifiable CA User request
to us by either:
Clicking here: https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out;
Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
Emailing us at: care@nuts.com; or
Sending us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
We endeavor to act on all opt-out requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within fifteen (15) business
days of the receipt of your request.
Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your
personal information over the past twelve (12) months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable CA User
request, we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we have shared that personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:
sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and
disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of
recipient obtained.
Deletion Request Rights
You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and
retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable CA User request, we will
delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our (their) records, unless
an exception applies; provided, however, that in some cases, strictly for regulatory compliance purposes and to
better evidence/honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests (and for no other purposes), we may retain certain items of
your personal information on a de-identified and aggregated basis in such a manner that the data no longer
identifies you.
We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:
Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you
requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with
you, or otherwise perform our obligations in connection with our contract/relationship with you.
Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, or prosecute
those responsible for such activities.
Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
Exercise free speech rights, ensure the right of another CA User to exercise her/his free speech rights or
exercise another right provided for by law.
Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.).
Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that
adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render
impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, but only if you previously provided informed
consent.
Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with CA User expectations based on your relationship
with us.
Comply with a legal obligation.
Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you
provided it.
Exercising Access, Data Portability and Deletion Rights
To exercise your access, data portability and/or deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable CA
User request to us by either:
Clicking here: https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request;
Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
Emailing us at: care@nuts.com; or
Sending us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf,
may make a verifiable CA User request related to your personal information.
You may only make a verifiable CA User request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period.
The verifiable CA User request must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify that you are: (1) the person about whom we
collected personal information; or (2) an authorized representative.
Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to
it.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or
authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you.  Making a verifiable CA
User request does not require that you create an account with us.  We will only use personal information
provided in a verifiable CA User request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
Response Timing and Format
We endeavor to respond to all verifiable CA User requests within forty-five (45) days of the receipt thereof.
If we require more time (up to ninety (90) days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in
writing.  We will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option.  Any disclosures that
we provide will only cover the twelve (12) month period preceding the receipt of your verifiable request.  The
response that we provide will also explain the reasons that we cannot comply with a request, if applicable.  For
data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable
and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable CA User request unless it is excessive,
repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.  If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we
made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.
Non-Discrimination
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we
will not:
Deny you goods or services;
Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other
benefits, or imposing penalties;
Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; and/or
Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality
of goods or services.
Changes to these Privacy Provisions
We reserve the right to amend these Privacy Provisions in our discretion and at any time. When we make changes
to these Privacy Provisions, we will notify you by email or through a notice on the Site's homepage.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or comments about these Privacy Provisions, our Privacy Policy, the ways in which we
collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your
rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact us by either:
Clicking here: https://nuts.com/contact;
Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
Emailing us at: care@nuts.com; or
Sending us U.S. mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.
About usContact usYour accountEasy reorderShippingTestimonialsWholesaleMediaHelpCareersPrivacy policyCA privacy noticeT & CDo not sell my infoAccessibilitySitemap
